John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1945-1972, undated; 5
  - Defense, 1950-1972, undated; 3
    - Army, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Army, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Army, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Army, Data, 1963 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Army, Defense Supply Agency, 1971 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Army, Press Release, 1966 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Army, Technical Liaison Office, 1965 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Army, Technical Liaison Office, 1966 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 320, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Data, 1963 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Employment Information, 1966 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Federal Employment Oversees, 1972 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Navy, Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Navy, Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Navy, Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Navy, Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Navy, Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Navy, Data, 1963-1970 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Navy, Marine Corps, 1965-1971 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Navy, Nacogdoches Jet Training Base Selection, 1955 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Navy, Navy Guide for Retired Personnel and Their Families, 1965 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Navy, Regular Naval Reserve Officers Corps Program, 1964 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Navy, Regulations Governing the Admission of Candidates into the US Naval Academy as Midshipmen and Sample Examination Questions, 1956 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Navy, Report to the Congress of the US-Need for Improvements in Supply and Maintenance Support for F-4 Aircraft, 1967 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Navy, SST and Sonic Boom Handbook, 1968 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - National Guard Bureau, Annual Report-Fiscal Year 1966 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - National Guard Bureau, 1970 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - News Releases, 1965 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Opinion Ballots, 1964 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1967-1971 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Project Themis, 1967 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Buildings with Fallout Shelter, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Current Status of Civil Defense in Schools, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Publications, How to Support Members of the Armed Forces Overseas, undated (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Guide to Specifications and Standards of the Federal Government, 1962 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Publications, How to Buy Surplus Personal Property, 1959 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Publications, How to Buy Surplus Personal Property, 1954 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Publications, How to Sell to Agencies within the Dept. of Defense, 1958 (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Index of Audit Reports Issued to the Congress, Its Committees and Members on Dept. of Defense Activities-Fiscal Years 1956 through 1963 (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Industrial College of the Armed Forces Catalog, 1957 (Box 324, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Meetings that Move, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Military Posts and Camps, 1969 (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Publications, National Resources Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 324, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Personal and Family Survival, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Product Qualification and Qualified Product Lists, 1962 (Box 324, Folder 17)
    - Publications, Proposed National Reserve Plan-In Defense of Freedom, undated (Box 324, Folder 18)
    - Publications, Publications Index, 1966 (Box 324, Folder 19)
    - Publications, Realistic Approach to Civil Defense, undated (Box 324, Folder 20)
    - Publications, School Boards Plan for Civil Defense, 1965 (Box 324, Folder 21)
    - Publications, Selling to the Military, undated (Box 324, Folder 22)
    - Publications, Voting Information, 1962 (Box 324, Folder 23)
    - Samuels & Co., Inc.-Defense Personnel Support Center, 1967 (Box 324, Folder 24)
    - Schools for Dependents, 1964 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Surplus Property, 1965-1966 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Corps, 1966 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - United States Information Agency, 1967 (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1972, undated; 4
    - Administration on Aging, 1967 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Children's Bureau, 1954-1961 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - General, 1971 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - General, 1972 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Data, 1963 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Food & Drug Administration, 1966-1968 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Food & Drug Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Food & Drug Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 1971 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - New Waverly Center, 1969 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Office of Education, Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Office of Education, Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Office of Education, General, 1964 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Office of Education, General, 1965 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Office of Education, General, 1966 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Office of Education, General, 1967-1968 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Office of Education, General, 1969 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Office of Education, General (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Office of Education, General (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Office of Education, 1971 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Office of Education, 1972 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Office of Education, Data, 1966-1969 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Office of Education, Data, 1970 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Office of Education, Data, 1972 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Office of Education, Head Start Program, 1969 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Office of Education, Head Start Program, 1970-1971 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Office of Education, Higher Education, 1965-1972 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Office of Education, International Exchange Program, 1966 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Office of Education, National Defense Student Loan Program, 1965-1966 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Office of Education, National Defense Student Loan Program, 1967-1971 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Office of Education, Teacher Corps, 1969 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - Office of Education, Training, 1967 (Box 330, Folder 10)
    - Office of Education, Upward Bound, 1971 (Box 330, Folder 11)
    - Pesticides, 1969 (Box 330, Folder 12)
    - Programs for the Handicapped, 1971 (Box 330, Folder 13)
    - Proposal, A Consortium for the Development of Educational Professionals, 1970 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Proposal, New Answers to the Questions of Rural and Urban Existence, 1970 March 11 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Public Health Service, 1965-1971 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Public Health Service, Data, 1970 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Public Health Service, Hill-Burton Program, 1964 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Publications, A Guide for Repayment, Deferment, and Cancellation of Health Professions Student Loans, 1969 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Publications, A National Survey of the Impacts of Head Start Centers on Community Institutions, 1970 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Administration of Public laws 874 & 815, 1966 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Publications, AID for Community Hospitals and Other Health Facilities, 1962 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Aids to Students, 1966 (Box 331, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Beaumont Remedial Clinic, undated (Box 331, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Better Education for Handicapped Children, 1970 (Box 331, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Books, 1971-1972 (Box 331, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Church and State, Vol. 24, No. 2, 1971 (Box 331, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Combined Effort for: Community Facilities + Community Programs, undated (Box 331, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Department of Public Welfare, Annual Report, 1962 (Box 331, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Education of Handicapped Children, 1971 (Box 331, Folder 17)
    - Publications, Education Professions Development Act, 1970 (Box 331, Folder 18)
    - Publications, Education Service Center, Region VI Year III, A Prospectus, 1969 (Box 331, Folder 19)
    - Publications, Education II — The Social Imperative, 1971 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Emerging Trends, undated (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Estimates of School Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Fact Book, Office of Education Programs, 1967 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Federal Support to Universities and Colleges, 1967 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Federally Insured Student Loans, 1971 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Financial Aid for College Students: Graduate, 1963 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Financial Aid for Higher Education, 1969 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Financial Assistance for College Students, 1965 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - Publications, From High School through College with Financial Assistance, 1965 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Futures in Education, 1969 (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Good Training Good Jobs, 1968 (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Handbook for Teacher Aides, undated (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Health Facility Construction, 1962 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Health Professions: Scholarship Program, 1969 (Box 332, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Health Professions: Student Loan Program, 1969 (Box 332, Folder 17)
    - Publications, Hill-Burton Publications, An Annotated Bibliography, 1963-19664 (Box 332, Folder 18)
    - Publications, Hill-Burton State Plan Data, 1962-1964 (Box 332, Folder 19)
    - Publications, Indicators, 1964-1965 (Box 332, Folder 20)
    - Publications, Institutions of Higher Education, 1971 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Learning for Earning: New Opportunities for Paycheck Education, 1969 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Legislative Achievement and Activities, 1964 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Publications: More EducationELMore Opportunity, 1969 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Publications, National Defense Student Loan Program, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Publications, National Teacher Corps, 1966 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Publications, NH Publications List, 1969-1972 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Nursing — Profession for You?, 1962 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Open the Door to Better Libraries, undated (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Outdoor Recreation, 1964 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Podiatry and the Nation’s Health, 1962 (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Pogo Primer for parents, TV Division, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Public Health Service Regulations, Part 53, 1959, 1962-1963 (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Rankings of the States, 1971-1972 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Research and Related Programs of the National Cancer Institute, 1969 (Box 333, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Revised Statement of Policies for School Desegregation Plans, 1996 (Box 333, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Schools of Professional Nursing, 1962 (Box 333, Folder 17)
    - Publications, Serving Region Seven, 1968 (Box 333, Folder 18)
    - Publications, Teacher Exchange Opportunities, 1964 (Box 333, Folder 19)
    - Publications, Teaching as a Career, 1959 (Box 333, Folder 20)
    - Publications, Teaching Opportunities, 1959, 1964 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Publications, The Community is the Classroom, undated (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Publications, The First Work of These Times, 1965 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Publications, The Higher Education Act, Fiscal Year 1970 Awards (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Publications, The Hill-Harris Amendments of 1964 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Publications, The National Defense Graduate Fellowship Program, 1960 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Publications, The National Defense Student Loan Program, 1959, 1965 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Publications, The National Teacher Corps, 1966 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Publications, U.S. News and World Report index, 1970 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Utilizing Teacher Aides, undated (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Vista Volunteer, Changes, 1970 (Box 334, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Where the Money Is, 1969 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Publications, You Can Go To College, 1965-1966 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Social Security Administration, 1953-1957 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Social Security Administration, 1958-1965 (Box 334, Folder 15)
    - Social Security Administration, 1966 (Box 334, Folder 16)
    - Social Security Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Social Security Administration, 1969 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Social Security Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Social Security Administration, 1970 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Social Security Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Social Security Administration- Moreland, 1972 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1954-1972; 5
    - General, 1965-1966 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - General, 1967 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - General, 1970-1971 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - General, 1972 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Data, 1970, 1972 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Federal Water Pollution Control, 1968 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1954-1955 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1958-1959 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1961-1962 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1963 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1965, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1969 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Houston County Hospital, 1959 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Office of Congressional Liaison, 1965 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, 1967 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Housing for Senior Citizens, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Housing the Economically and Socially Disadvantaged Groups in the Population, 1961 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Public Housing, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Publications, U.S. Housing: A New Program, 1958 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Ways and means of Providing Housing, 1960 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Sewer Bond Program Orange, Texas, 1966 (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Urban Renewal Administration, 1965 (Box 338, Folder 13)
  - Interior, 1952-1972, undated; 6
    - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, 1965 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Cayuga School Case, 1971 (Box 338, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 338, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - General, 1964-1967 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Interior, General, 1971-1972 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Dams, 1965 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Data, 1963-1970 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Employment Opportunities with National Park Concessioners, 1965 Season (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Federal Register, 1966 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Fish and Wildlife, 1962-1970 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Geological Survey, 1970 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Grand Canyon Dams, 1966 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Heavy Metals Program, 1967 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Indian Affairs, 1970 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Indian Arts and Craft Board, 1967 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - Land Management, 1970 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - Land and Water Conservation Fund Program, 1965 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Land and Water Conservation, 1970 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Mustang Island, 1970 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - National Parks, 1965-1969 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - National Park Service, 1970-1972 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket, 1967 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - National Park Service, Big Thicket, 1972 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - News Article Releases and Data, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - News Release, 1966-1967 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Oil and Gas Corporation, 1966 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Outdoor Recreation, 1966-1967 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Outdoor Recreation, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Outdoor Recreation, 1970-1972 (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - Padre Island, 1972 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Areas Administered by the National Park Service, 1965 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Big Texas Thicket, 1967-1970 (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Career Employment in the National Park Service, 1961 (Box 342, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Career Opportunities, 1963 (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Comprehensive River Basin Planning, 1967 (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Cost Sharing with Industry?, 1967 (Box 342, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Engineering Aids and Technicians, 1963 (Box 342, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Facts About Earnings While Receiving Payments, 1954 (Box 342, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Facts for Farm Families, 1954 (Box 342, Folder 17)
    - Publications, Facts for Those Who are Disabled, 1954 (Box 342, Folder 18)
    - Publications, Facts for Household Workers, 1954 (Box 342, Folder 19)
    - Publications, Federal Assistance in Outdoor Recreation, 1966 (Box 342, Folder 20)
    - Publications, Federal Focal Point in Outdoor Recreation, 1964 (Box 342, Folder 21)
    - Publications, Federal Reclamation Projects, 1966 (Box 342, Folder 22)
    - Publications, Future Parks for the Nation, 1963 (Box 342, Folder 23)
    - Publications, Guidelines for the Prevention, Control, and Abatement of Water Pollution, 1967 (Box 342, Folder 24)
    - Publications, Guides to Outdoor Recreation Areas and Facilities, 1966 (Box 342, Folder 25)
    - Publications, Incentives to Industry for water Pollution Control: Policy Considerations, 1967 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Land and Water Conservation Fund Act, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Manpower and Training Needs in Water Pollution Control, 1967 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Migratory Bird Regulations, 1958 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Publications, National Parks, 1965 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Publications, National Rivers and Harbors, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Oil Pollution, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Outdoor Recreation Action, 1971 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Padre Island, 1970 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Quotes, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Redwoods-to-the-Sea, undated (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Seasonal Employment, 1965-1971 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Seasons for Migratory Game Birds, 1956 (Box 343, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Sierra Club Bulleting, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Smoke Signals, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Stewards of the Land, undated (Box 343, Folder 16)
    - Publications, The Cost of Clean Water, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 17)
    - Publications, The Living Wilderness, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 18)
    - Publications, The National Register of Historic Places, 1970 (Box 343, Folder 19)
    - Publications, The Nature of Eastex, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 20)
    - Publications, The Recreation/Conservation Sticker, 1965 (Box 343, Folder 21)
    - Publications, The Southwesterner, 1970,1972 (Box 343, Folder 22)
    - Publications, Washington Shuttle Tour, undated (Box 343, Folder 23)
    - Publications, Water Pollution Control, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 24)
    - Publications, Water Pollution Control Training Program, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 25)
    - Publications, Water Quality Standards, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 26)
    - Publications, Wild and Scenic Rivers, 1970 (Box 343, Folder 27)
    - Publications, Wilderness Study: Padre Island National Seashore, 1971 (Box 343, Folder 28)
    - Publications, Woodlands Trail, undated (Box 343, Folder 29)
    - Reclamation, 1965-1972 (Box 343, Folder 30)
    - Redwood National Park and Seashore Plan, 1967 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - Justice, 1952-1972; 7
    - Bureau of Narcotics and Dangerous Drugs, 1972 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights Bill, 1964 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1960 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Data, 1963 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - FBI, 1965-1970 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1954-1964 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1965-1968 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1969-1971 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1970 (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - Parole Board, 1965-1973 (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Annual Report of the Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1967 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Fact Book: A Question and Answer Discussion of the Nonimmigrant Visa Act of 1971 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Immigration and Nationality Act, 1965, 1970-1971 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Naturalization Requirements and General Information, 1969 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Publications, The Civil Rights Act of 1964 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Publications, United States Immigration Laws, 1971 (Box 346, Folder 6)
  - Labor, 1952-1972, undated; 8
    - Administration, 1958, 1963 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Alien Employment, 1966 (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Apprenticeship and Training, 1965 (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Cascade Employers Association, Inc., 1967 (Box 346, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 346, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 346, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 346, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 346, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 347, Folder 6)